Ryan先生 相信我 没有人在玩弄我们  我们是不容摆布的
Mr. Ryan, trust me, no one is playing us. We are unplayable.
我想听听关于性骚扰指控的更多细节
I'd like to hear more on the charges of molestation.
请继续
Go ahead.
请继续我想听听关于性骚扰指控的更多细节
Go ahead.  I'd like to hear more on the charges of molestation.
他的手曾经接触过你的睾丸吗?
Was there ever any contact between testicles and hands?
不 没有
No. Never.
我的 蛋蛋们
My... spheres
一向穿戴整齐
were always clothed.
我当时在工作场所 所以我
I was in the workplace, so I--
他总会同时摸你的两个睾丸吗?
Did he always grope both testicles?
不好意思 能换一个男委员
I'm sorry, but can I be asked that question
来问我这种问题吗?
by a male committee member?
不 由我来问
No, I asked the question.
很抱歉  我忘了你的问题是什么
I'm sorry. I forgot the question.
那个欺凌你的人是不是摸了你的两个睾丸?
Did your abuser touch both of your testicles?